Iván Trejo

Full Stack Developer PERN | Javascript | Typescript | HTML | CSS | Python | Git | Github | nodeJS | ReactJS | ReduxJS | ExpressJS | Sequelize | Prisma | PostgreSQL | MySQL | UX

Location: Sevilla - Spain

(+57) 3202430789

Email: ivanjtrejoc@gmail.com

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ivanjtrejoc/

Portfolio: https://ivantrejo.vercel.app/

Github: https://github.com/ivantrejoc

Full Stack Developer with a background in banking, business, and digital marketing, this experience allowed me to gain a deep understanding of banking and administrative processes and helped me to develop soft skills like teamwork, results orientation, leadership, time management, and self-discipline.

I specialize in business-adapted solutions development, using Front-end tools (HTML, CSS, WordPress React, Nextjs, Vite, Redux, Zustand), Back-end (Express, Node), and database (Sequelize, Prisma, PostgreSQL, MySQL, MongoDB), into Agile environments.

EXPERIENCE:

Full Stack Developer

Soluciones Star. Medellín – Colombia (Full time – remote)

Apr 2024 - Jul 2024

- Developed and assisted in multiple projects such as landing pages and responsive web applications, primarily focused on the frontend area using WordPress and plugins such as Elementor, SiteOrigin page builder, and AOS animations.
- Developed projects with Vite, React, and style libraries such as MUI and TailwindCSS, GSAP
 animations, and state management with Redux toolkit and Zustand, all following UX/UI guidelines
 established in the Figma designs provided by the design area.

Full Stack Developer

Nov 2023 - Feb 2024

Freelance Medellín – Colombia (Part-time – remote).

Developed full-stack projects for personal clients. Between highlighting e-commerce projects and tailored web applications to gym operations management, developing specific features according to clients' needs. The stack applied includes Nodejs, express, Sequelize, PostgreSQL, Mysql, React, TailwindCSS, CSS styled components among others.

Full Stack Web Developer

Jul 2023 – Aug 2023

Academic experience at Henry Bootcamp. Buenos Aires – Argentina (remote)

Project: Wanderlust.

Deploy: https://wanderlust-phi.vercel.app/

Tourism E-commerce. My main contribution was the development of routes and controllers into the backend, PayPal payment runway integration, and support on frontend admin views. Features: Destination search, filters, sorts, third-party authentication, shopping cart, payment runway, travel schedule.

Junior Full Stack Developer

Mar 2023 - Jun 2023

Henry Bootcamp (academic experience). Buenos Aires, Argentina (remote).

Project: Pokemon

Deploy: https://pokemonivan.vercel.app

App to render and create Pokemon characters. Features: landing, filters, sorts, characters search, character creation form, DBB to characters storage, Pokemon API connection from the backend.

Junior Full Stack Developer

Nov 2022 – Jan 2023

Henry Bootcamp (academic experience). Buenos Aires, Argentina (remote).

Project: Rick and Morty

Repository: https://github.com/ivantrejoc/rick_and_morty.git

App to render Rick and Morty characters. Features: login, filters, sorts, random button, characters search, R&M API connection from the front end.

Full Stack Teaching Assistant

May 2023 - Oct 2023

Henry Bootcamp (academic experience). Buenos Aires, Argentina (remote, part-time).

- Lead a group of students to integrate into the Henry Bootcamp.
- Provide support to solve exercises and promote a culture of group collaboration (pair programming).
- Suggest new ideas to enhance processes within the bootcamp.

Web Developer / Content Manager

Feb 2021 - Jul 2023

Now Agency. Medellín, Colombia (remote, full-time).

 Developed websites for agency clients working on 2 people team. Highlighting landing pages, portfolios, and e-commerce projects, using Wordpress, Wordpress plugins and Webflow, React, NextJs, Node, Express, Sequelize, and SQL/ No SQL databases. Applying clean styles, responsive design, and respecting UX/UI requirements.

Highlight projects:

- https://nowagency.com.co/
- https://worksplaceus.com/
- https://vivesanoprime.org/
- Created social media content for agency clients' accounts, increasing their audience by 25% in the first 6 months. Utilized storytelling, AIDA, and PAS tools and marketing strategies.

TECH STACK:

Programming languages: Javascript, Typescript, HTML5, CSS3.

CMS: WordPress, Elementor, SiteOrigin page builder, AOS animations, etc.

Frontend: React, NextJS, Vite, Redux, Zustand, MUI TailwindCSS, Bootstrap, Cloudinary, Babel,

Tremor, GSAP animations.

Backend: Node, Express.

ORM's: Sequelize, Prisma.

Databases: PostgreSQL, My SQL, MongoDB.

CI/CD: Git, Docker.

Other tools: Figma, Insomnia, Slack, Trello, and Google Suite.

Management: SCRUM.

EDUCATION:

- Full Stack Web Developer, Henry Bootcamp. 800 hours, practical-theoretical course. 2023.
- Bachelor in Accounting, Universidad de los Andes, Venezuela, 2006 2013.
- High School Diploma, Colegio Arzobispo Silva, Venezuela, 1999 2004.

ADDITIONAL EDUCATION:

- Master in Python, Django, and Flask. Udemy is in progress.
- UX design: user experience UX/UI + Figma 2024. Udemy 2024.
- SCRUM Fundamentals Certified. SCRUMstudy. 2023
- Digitalize your business step by step with Google tools. 2023.
- Web Development Introduction I. Google Learn Digital. 2022.
- Web Development Introduction II. Google Learn Digital. 2022.
- Digital Marketing. Google Learn Digital. 2022.
- Basic Fundamentals and Programming Logic with Python. Fundación Escuela Latinoamericana de Redes. 2022.

LANGUAGES:

- Native Spanish speaker.
- English C2 proficient (listening and reading) B2 speaking.